My gutted room
It's huge!
Look at the post.
It's true, it's gonna rain.
Wow.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hello, I'm Haruyo Yamaguchi of Hinataka46. I am Haruyo Yamaguchi from Hinataka46.
This time, I've returned to my hometown, Yunako, Tottori.
Since it's summer vacation, I have Honoko back home with me.
Hello, I'm Haruyo Yamaguchi of Hinatoko 46. Hi, I'm Honoko Hirao. I'm Honoko Hirao.
Hi, I'm Honoko Hirao. Pleased to meet you.
We are back together.
This time, I would like to enjoy Tottori Prefecture with you.
Let's go a lot.
We will visit places of memories.
Let's go!
There it is.
A car.
Please.
Please take care of it.
I've been coming from Tottori to various stores without knowing it.
That's right.
You came from the west or something, didn't you?
But I went there.
I went to Saisei in Tottori.
I was so impressed that I went there about seven times in one month.
That's too many times.
I went there.
I was on summer vacation, wasn't I?
That's right. We are too.
I have a lot of family at home, so there might be a lot of people there.
Are there a lot of people in your house? Right now.
No, not right now.
Maybe at night. There might be a lot of people there at night.
I'm glad.
Here they are.
What a house.Amazing house.
Amazing house.
I think there's a garden, too.
A garden.
There's a raccoon.
Look.
How cute!
There are amazing frogs.
This is Kinjiro Miyamiya.
I'm back.
Yes, I'm back. Hello. Pleased to meet you.
I am Kinjiro Miyamiya. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I'm Miyamiya Kinjiro. Hello. Pleased to meet you.
Oh, it's so cute.
A frog.
I can see that.
I said it.
Thank you. Nice to meet you.
Come here.
How old are you? How old?
He's talking.
Please, talk to me.
Hello, hello.
Please, talk.
Say hello.
Okay, okay.
I'll play with you. I'll play with you a lot.
I'll play catch with you.
Come here. Come here.
Come sit here.
What game are you playing these days?
Pikmin.
Cute. You play Pikmin?
They're new. They're new.You've got a new one, right?
They recently came out with Coke.
You like spring pop?
LOL!
You like it?
You like Spring Pop?
You just say yes.
Okay, I'm going upstairs.
This way.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Japanese house.
We have a lot of family.
It's so big!
There's so much stuff!
Oh, no, wait!
Oh, no, no, no!
We've got merchandise!
Oh, no!
Excuse me.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, there's so much stuff!
Excuse me for interrupting.
This is Rio's...
This is Rio's room.
Wow, it's huge!
It's so big!
There are so many goods!
There are a lot of goods of Hinata
Wow!
Oh, Remind!
It's so thick!
There really are a lot of goods
It's so much like that
A long time ago
Hiragana zelkova days, right?
I used to collect these too.I used to collect these too.
It's a random prize.
Oh, you mean the ones that you just flick?
Yes, yes, you just flick it, and then you put it in carefully.
I put them in very carefully.
Look at this.
This is me.
This is when I was a goldsmith.
There he is!
So young!
Seriously, I don't even wear makeup anymore.
Here you go.
I was just toweling off.
Kosaka-san's
Hiragana Keyaki era.
A towel from the Hiragana Keyaki era.
has been unearthed.
Hinano-chan!
The very first Hinano-chan!
This is Hinano-chan!
The first Asha.
The first Asha!
She brought us some amazing fruit!
Haruyo-san's twin sister.
They look exactly alike.
Come here, Haruyo-san!
Oh, my God...
We can switch.
It's like a job.
You even sound alike.
The same voice?
The same.
I can't tell which one's speaking.
I can definitely tell.
Okay, let me guess.
Which one said it?
I closed my eyes.I closed my eyes.
Hiraoka Naka.
I'm sure she's your sister.
Younger sister.
She has a different personality.
Very different.
I can see that.
I really do.
Very funny. Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
It was my sister.
Hi!
Bon appétit!
First time
Melongo.
Is it good? Is it cold?
It's good.
My sister loves melons.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Oh, my God.
It's so good!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hari-Usan, can you do that for me?
I'll take care of it.
Mapparoo!
Did you see that?
Thank you very much.
I love you so much.
Really?
I need to check something.
At the very beginning.
When we get to Tottori...
I can call you Haruyo-chan.
I negotiated with her.
I did, didn't I?
This is Tottori Prefecture.We are in Tottori Prefecture.
It's OK.
Yay!
I'll call you Haruyo-chan.
I'm so glad!
And Haruyo-chan...
What do you want me to say, "Haruyo-chan"?
You said it yourself.
I don't know.
I'm doing my own research.
Researching what?
You're Haruyo-chan.
You call me Hirao-chan.
I don't like it.
I want you to call me Hirao-chan.
What would you like? Like Hirao? Hirao would be nice. Hirao? I'll go with Hirao.
Does it suit you? Then call me Hiraho. Today I'll call you Hiraho. Not today.
From now on? I'll call you Heiho for the rest of my life.
Where did you come from? Haruyo-san. Haruyo-chan.
This is Sakaimi's bathroom.
Can you see it?
There's a place called Shigeru Mizuki Road.
Here's another one.
What's this? It's a rat man.
Look at this post.
And over here is a big...
There it is.
There's a lot of stuff on the road.
There are a lot of souvenirs.
Yes, there's a lot of food and drink.
I want to buy something for the members.
That's nice.
Speaking of souvenirs...
Like the boy temple we went to together.
Yes, I like Kitaro.
I love him so much I'd like to buy him something.He loves Kitaro so much, I'd like to buy him something.
You were in love with him, weren't you?
My first love was Kitaro.
I found Iwama's fortune. I'll draw it.
I'm counting on you.
Great, what's with this system?
He's saying something.
He's saying "Kitaro.
Oh, he's here.
I'm in. - Oh, man...
He's coming.
I knew it. That's what he meant.
It's here. Okay.
I got it.
I'll open it.
It's a fortune, right?
Here we go.
Ready?
Kitchen
Kitchen.
Same here.
Health.
Recovered with good doctor's orders
Same.
Exactly.
Wow. I drew the exact same omikuji.
It says, "Let yourself go once in a while.
I'm going to let go today.
I'll let go today.
Thank you very much.
I'll take it
I got it.
Crab.
Crab is delicious, isn't it?
It smells good. Bon appétit.
It's hot.
It's hot.Hot.
That's hot.
This is, yes, часть.
Oh!
Here comes the response.
I used to buy souvenirs like yokai manju (monster buns)
Specter buns are good, aren't they?
It's good, isn't it, guys?
I bought some souvenirs here, yokai manju.
I've been here many times
You come here a lot, don't you?
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Excuse me.
I'm craving it most of all.
Manjuu dumplings!
Looks delicious!
Introduce, introduce!
This is the one with black vanilla flavor!
Looks so delicious!
I've never seen this before.
So cute!
Youkai Shinmei
The pattage is...
There are various flavors!
Black vanilla
This is nice, isn't it?
Souvenirs!
Chilled manjuu!
Let's buy it!
What flavor?
Vanilla is good.
I've never had it before.
Let's have another one.
Let's have one.
I found a great latrine.
What character?What character?
This is a youtuber.
He's a YouTuber.
This is the Rat Man.
I'm
I'm the eyeball guy. - I'm the eyeball guy. - I'm the eyeball guy.
Bon appétit!
Yum.
Delicious!
Mappal
Oh, I made a mistake.
Mappal is normal.
Mappal
Mappal is so cute!
I love it so much!
My stomach is full.
My personal mission for today
I wanted to buy some souvenirs for my beloved Yoko
I wanted to buy some souvenirs from Kitaro.
I want to buy one too.
Really?
Don't say it like that.
I found it.
A good souvenir shop.
I'll go here.
I'll look for souvenirs.
I like Kitaro.
I want to give it to you.
I want to give it to a senior member.
I don't know what would be good.
She likes Kitaro, too.
I said I like Momo too.
Really?
I like...
At the same time.
But I'd like something.
Buy some snacks.Buy some snacks.
What can I get you?
It's so cute.
There's all kinds of cups.
They're all the same!
Did you find anything good? Haruyo.
Let's see...
Socks are easy to get together.
Socks?
I'll get Kitaro's.
Matching socks.
Cute!
I got a souvenir!
Yay, yay!
Wear them, everyone!
These are cute.
With a note.
I can use them.
Surveys.
There are a lot of opportunities to send out questionnaires.
So I thought a file would be nice.
I'm a little choosy.
Here.
Isn't this interesting?
It's really good.
I'll take this one.
I'm really excited about this one.
I'll buy this one.
Okay, I'll buy it.
This time the pikus is 300 yen back.
Thank you.
Well, you got a good deal.
It was a good shopping experience.
I enjoyed a lot.
It was fun.
Shall we go home?
Let's go home.
I'm hungry, aren't you?You are hungry, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I am. So, today, what a surprise,
Yes.
At Mr. Kallio's house,
I'm going to stay at Mr. Kallio's house.
That's right.
It's the first time a member is staying here.
Oh, really?
Yes, I'm sure. I've never had a member over before.
Well, I've never been to my parents' house before,
It's kind of a family home, isn't it?
What do you want to do? I guess so.
Yes, there was. Hina and Zuka channel.
Yes, that's right.
I want to go to Tottori. I want to go to Tottori.
I wrote that.
So you told me that.
Yes, I did.
That makes me happy.
So, I'm already hung up on it.
I was really happy.
I was happy.
It was a lot of fun.
No, me too. Me too.
You couldn't sleep?
I couldn't sleep at all.
It's Tottori, after all.
That's right. I did.
I don't have time to come here often.
I'll have a bowl of rice.
Bon appétit.
I can't eat.
Sushi.
Sushi and meat salad
Best with
Everything togetherEverything together.
I'll take it.
This is amazing!
Spicy.
Spicy is good
Egg omelet
Yay!
Delicious!
Delicious
Sweet?
Sweet.
Is it salty?
Very tasty.
It's delicious.
The meat is delicious.
It's good.
That's good.
Fried chicken and mother
Handmade.
Thank you.
Your sister's feet are sweating.
Your sister's feet are sweating
Happy Birthday
To you
Sing it for me
Happy birthday to you
For now
Happy Birthday
To you
Happy Birthday to you
for now
How do you like it?
Thank you very much. I'm glad.
You gave me one.
Thank you very much.
A present from the Yamaguchi family.A present from the Yamaguchi family.
Oh, my God! Are you sure?
Thank you very much.
I'm turning 20.
You're an adult.
You can drink.
Yes, I can.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Want some?
Bon appétit.
Post-workout experience
Delicious
Bordering on tropical
Happy with whatever comes along
Happy with anything
I'm happy about anything that comes my way
I don't know what it is.
Hand cream.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Hand cream in the summer?
I use it.
That's good.
I'm glad.
I took a bath.
If we were on a school trip, we'd have been told to go to bed.
But...
It's not over until it's over.
It's not over.
We've brought games for each other today.
That's right.
Play the game.
I'm going to play.
I'd like to play.
Yes, I'm already relaxing
I'm getting sleepy now.
Well, I'm sure we'll go to many places again tomorrow.
I haven't decided yet.I haven't decided yet.
That's right, not yet.
I'm thinking I'll wake up tomorrow and decide.
That's right.
Then I'd like to go to bed.
Okay, then.
Good night.
Bye-bye.
Good morning.
It's the second day.
Today, I'd like to go eat some delicious food in Tottori.
I'm fully prepared.
Oh, there they are!
They're here!
Nice view!
You must be doing a lot of skiing there!
I'll teach you how to ski, too.
Wow, here we are!
Here we are in Taisei!
Here we are! Milk Village!
I'm so happy.
Yes, it is.
Wow!
It's open.
I want to show you.
I want to show it to you.
Look at this.
The view is amazing.
Wow, Tottori.
It's so green! It's annoying.
The soft-serve ice cream here is delicious!
No, it's the best!
Let's eat it right away!
It smells so good!
Let's eat!
Let's go!
Thank you very much.Thank you.
I got it.
I got it!
I got what I wanted.
I'm so happy.
There's quite a bench and everything.
Yes, sir.
Now, I'll have it before it melts.
It's too rich, it's melting, already.
Delicious!
It's the best in Japan!
The best in Japan!
You must try this!
Yeah.
Mmm!
Masaru!
Oh! He's asleep!
Mwah! Delicious!
There it is!
I got it!
I'm out again today!
Hiro, what do you want to do?
You know, I want to exercise!
You're good at exercise, aren't you, Hiro?
I'm really good at it!
I think I can do 50m in 6.3 seconds.
Look! It's this big!
Oh, my God!
Let's run!
We've got to run!
I'll be a mute!
Okay, let's go!
Three, two, one.
One.
~~~~!
I'm stuck!
I guess I don't get enough exercise.Not enough exercise, huh?
Hiraho is good with cows.
That's right. I'm quite good at it.
I can touch them.
That's great.
Well, I'm looking for the countryside.
Hario? Hario-chan?
I haven't explained to you why I'm Hario-chan.
I haven't told you why I made this appointment.
I'm from Tottori Prefecture.
Actually...
We went to the same high school.
We had talked before we joined the group.
You like the hill road, don't you?
And he had some friends.
Yes, I did.
We were in the same grade, but different classes.
So when we met in the hallway...
I'd see them in the hallway and talk to them.
We talked.
So we knew each other a little bit.
So, you know, you see it like this.
One or two people are going public, right?
I think...
But it's an unveiling.
Yeah, they were unveiling.
I was so surprised.
I thought it was one of the girls in the photo.
I saw her face and saw her name.
What's that?
What's that? I don't get it.
Huh?
I remember that.
I have a memory of it.
I thought I had a memory of it.
Well, there was a flashback.
Yes, there was a wrinkle.
Yes, originally.That's right, originally.
That's why I became Haruyo-chan.
Yes, I became Haruyo-chan.
But you're going to leave again, aren't you?
Yes, that's right.
I knew it.
Even a little bit.
It's fine. You can call me "chan" if you want.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, just call me "chan" when you're comfortable.
Really?
Yeah. - Okay.
Well, I'm sorry if I did.
Not at all.
It's okay on my end.
Yes!
Okay, here we go.
For the record.
Yes, sir.
It's officially done.
It's officially approved.
It was good.
I'm glad.
Oh!
It's going to be a good picture.
Yes, for sure.
It's nice.
That's good.
A good, happy summer.
Behind the bus.
You're getting really good at this.
Quite a lot of baked goods here, too.
A little bit more for Haruyuu-chan
Fastball!
It's not often you get to see it from this position.
I'd like you to jump over to the other side of me.I'd like you to jump over to the other side of me.
Yes, sir.
That's great, but that's a light ball.
So I'm just supposed to copy that?
Wes tsitsu.
Wes tsitsu
Wow, tree.
Please.
Masai Kami
Donc
west
fighters
Well, that was fun!
It was a really good two days and one night trip!
It's not often that I get to go back to Tottori like this and hang out with the other members.
I'm so glad!
It was so much fun to hang out with people from Tottori!
Maybe we can bring other members again?
We'll cool down the numbers and gradually get together again.
Thank you so much for watching this show!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!